wpunlock.com 2014-10-10

# Privacy Policy

**What Information do We Collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: Name and E – Mail, You may however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your Information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the Following ways:

  1. To personalize your Experience (Your Information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  2. To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  3. To improve Customer Service (Your Information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  4. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the Safety of your personal information when you enter, submit or access your personal Information.

**Cookies and 3 rd Party Advertisement.**

  * Google as third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enabled it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * We allow third party companies to serve ads and / or Collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non – personally identifiable information (e.g., Click stream information, Browser type, time and date, subject of advertisement clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These Companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt – out of this type of advertising, you can visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Do we Disclose any information to outside Parties?**

We do not Sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information Confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or Safety. However, non – personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at out discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on or website, these third part sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have to responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our terms and Conditions section established the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at

<http://www.wpunlock.com/terms-and-conditions/>

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we Decide to Change our Privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This Policy was last modified on **13/07/2014**.

**Contacting Us**

If There are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

<http://www.wpunlock.com/contact-us/>
